(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.2",
"generated_at": "2026-08-29T23:30:10.894244",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.6-flash",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
チーム友達 チーム友達
Team Tomodachi, Team Tomodachi
俺たち何？え？チーム友達
What are we? Huh? Team Tomodachi
関西 関東 西 東
Kansai, Kanto, West, East,
北 南 チーム友達
North, South, Team Tomodachi
チーム友達 チーム友達
Team Tomodachi, Team Tomodachi
チーム チーム チーム友達
Team, Team, Team Tomodachi
俺たち何？え？チーム友達
What are we? Huh? Team Tomodachi
お好み焼き 食う 鶴橋
Eating okonomiyaki in Tsuruhashi
腹いっぱい 飯は美味い
Full stomach, the food is delicious
一人じゃ寂しいし電話きたり
I felt lonely alone, got a call
かけ直した後すぐ行く会いに
After calling back, I'm going right away to see you
T-E-A-M T-O-M-O-D-A-C-H-I
チーム友達 混ざり合い
Team Tomodachi, mixing together
契り交わし 飲んでる酒
Exchanging pacts, drinking sake
契り 契り 契り 契り
Pact, pact, pact, pact
契ろう 契ろう 契ろう 契ろう
Let's make a pact, let's make a pact, let's make a pact, let's make a pact
契り 契り 契り 契り
Pact, pact, pact, pact
契ろう 契ろう 契ろう 契ろう
Let's make a pact, let's make a pact, let's make a pact, let's make a pact
チーム友達 チーム友達
Team Tomodachi, Team Tomodachi
俺たち何？え？チーム友達
What are we? Huh? Team Tomodachi
関西 関東 西 東
Kansai, Kanto, West, East,
北 南 チーム友達
North, South, Team Tomodachi
チーム友達 チーム友達
Team Tomodachi, Team Tomodachi
チーム チーム チーム友達
Team, Team, Team Tomodachi
俺たち何？え？チーム友達
What are we? Huh? Team Tomodachi
チーム友達 チーム友達
Team Tomodachi, Team Tomodachi
チーム友達
Team Tomodachi
You know, come to think of it, it's been two years since we broke out of the cell, huh?
Yeah, time goes by fast, yeah.
We've been through a lot, right?
Huh? What? Hey, guys!
What's that over there?!
Huh? What is that?
Attention. Justice. Elizabeth Rose Bloodflame.
Initiating final warning protocol.
Five escapees detected from the cell.
Repeat: Five escapees detected from the cell.
Targets are as follows.
The Demon of Sound, Nerissa Ravencroft.
The Jewel of Emotions, Koseki Bijou.
The Fluffy One, Fuwawa Abyssgard.
The Fuzzy One, Mococo Abyssgard.
The Archiver, Shiori Novella.
All units, apprehend the Advent members immediately!
Oh my god! What do we do?!
Oh no, we're in trouble! It's payback time!
They're gonna catch us!
I can't go back! I can't go back!
What are we gonna do?!
Oh well, guess we're doomed!
Guys, think! There's gotta be a solution for this, right?
Piggyback ride! Come on, piggyback ride!
Get on! Piggyback ride! I'll carry you!
Okay, maybe not that one. Yeah, sorry.
There's gotta be something, like a Plan B or something we can do!
Bwahaha! Struggling already?
Pokey?! What are you doing here?!
You finally show your face, huh?!
Ask nicely enough, and maybe I'll save your skins.
Come on! Come on!
Here, I have a solution.
Mwah! Please help us, Pokey!
Don't resist! Help us, Pokey!
Hmph! I don't hate that.
If you manage to pass the little trial I've cooked up for you,
I'll whisk you away to a whole other realm...
One where your pesky pursuers can't reach you!
I mean, I guess that's our only option, huh?
Oh well, guess we will do it!
Alright. I've prepared something special. Arise, my go-karts!
Go-Karts?!
Wait, we don't have a license!
Why? What about it? When do the people seeing us even stop?
See this course? Time to tackle the 'Go-Kart Escape Challenge'!
Oh! Escape Challenge!
Yes, that's right. Take it from here, ankle-biter.
Who are you talking to, huh? Ankle-biter?!
Calm down there. Well, actually...
Alright team! Game rules are incoming, so make sure you better listen, okay?
Okay!
Yeah! Nice!
Wait, Bijou, how do you know the game rules?
It's the glasses! That's how she knows! Glasses!
Rule 1: Survive 2 laps with zombies on your tail!
Zombies?! Where?!
Remember, last year we beat up zombies?
Well, one of them went on a path to revenge, and now it's gonna run after you!
Oh, okay, sounds good!
Rule 2: Collect items for bonus points, but watch out for traps that deduct points!
Oh no! Deduct points?!
Rule 3: Victory is ours if we all get 30 points total!
30 points?! Easy, right? We can do that!
And now I will explain the course items!
I must run! - You must run? - Yeah, I must run.
I'm gonna live out my dreams while there's a track here! Just explain, ignore me!
Okay, isn't she listening? Wow, she's fast!
There are crystals on the field! Beautiful crystals over there!
Two more over there.
They are gacha!
You'll either gain points or lose points based on...
...but you don't know, so it's a risk every time.
Yeah, and then there is...
...the big Moai! The big Moai!
It will block your path.
It is minus 20 points if you hit it, so don't hit it.
Don't hit it! Yeah, don't hit it!
And then, the Pebble!
I have kidnapped one of my Pebbles to use as a sacrifice if you hit it...
...minus 5 points, but you know what? I don't think they'd mind if you hit it, to be honest.
And the items will change...
...depending on your first lap or second lap. You're doing two laps.
Two laps. Two laps.
You can run another two laps!
Yeah, no, I'm great.
I guess time to show you how it's done.
Show us! Go on! Go on!
All right, first lap, show us how to do it.
I'm ready!
Go! Go, Bijou!
First lap, first lap! She got the crystal! She makes a turn!
Second crystal! Watch out!
She's going so fast!
The zombie's actually speeding up!
Second lap, let's go! Let's go!
Another crystal!
She hit another one!
Watch out!
The zombie! Watch out!
The zombie's speeding up!
I think you got a bit of bad luck with that crystal at the end.
It's okay, that's a pretty good run. Did I do fast?
It's okay, that's a pretty good run. Did I go fast?
Did I go fast? You went so fast!
You almost hit the zombie, but you're okay!
You didn't die!
How many points did I get? How many points?
That's a good question. How many points did you get?
I think you got one point.
What? One point? After all that? One point.
Did I have bad gacha luck?
It's a group effort, we can still get points.
Yeah, I contributed one! One!
One is great! One is great!
You can have like the pro do all the work for you, right? Yeah!
Pro Mococo! Yeah, yeah! I count on you guys!
Next up is Shiori!
Show us how it's done, our fearless leader! I have a plan.
What's your plan?
You'll figure it out when I say plan!
Good luck, Shiori!
あの、ゾンビだ！　先導ゾンビ！
Um, it's a zombie! The zombie ahead!
はい、いい子ですね。いい子ですね。
Yes, good boy. Good boy.
Let's go! Yeah, that's a good idea.
Come on, let's go, let's go!
いい子ですね。走れ！
Good boy. Run!
She's running! Get away!
What is she doing?
Get away! Get away!
Yeah! Yeah! Yeah!
It's like driving in New York!
Only thing I got... That's okay, I'll figure it out.
How is this driving in New York?
Okay, okay, okay!
You didn't catch him, but you sure gave him a run for his money!
I didn't care about the points, I just wanted to run them over!
Understandable.
How many points did I get?
Three points! Three points!
That's for running you over.
That's three points! That's pretty good! That's better than one!
So we have four! Alright, Fuwawa's turn!
Do you think you can do it?
Get four points! You can do it, I know you can!
The zombie is not going to run away anymore, so...
I think it's tired.
It's easier, you can outrun it. I'm the best driver!
Go, Fuwawa!
Go, Fuwawa! Go!
You're kind of going slow!
What do you mean? I want to go safe!
It's very safe driving!
Why am I so slow? But the zombie...
It's so slow!
Go, Fuwawa, go!
A crystal! Oh no!
Fire crystal!
It's okay, it's okay!
Go, go, go, go, go!
Go, Fuwawa!
Why is it so slow this time? Go faster!
Crystal, crystal! Ah, wrong crystal!
Watch out, watch out! Zombie, watch out!
She dodged it!
Is that the first lap still?
This is the second one now!
Zombie, zombie!
Hurry, Fuwawa!
Go, go, go, go!
You can do it!
She dodged, she dodged!
Ice crystal! Nice!
Fire crystal!
Yay! Finish!
Speed isn't that important, but the points are, right?
Fuwawa, I think you did really well!
So far, you're our top performer today with...
14 points!
Fuwawa carry!
What's the math? 17?
18!
You got three and you got one, so yeah, 18.
No, no, we got 14 points.
14 points!
Next is Mococo! Count the points, okay?
Count on me!
Go, Mococo!
You got this, Mococo!
I'll be fast, eventually.
It's a slow burn.
Oh, ice crystal!
Watch out, watch out!
She's fast!
Look at her go! She's so fast!
Look at her dodge the zombie!
You're doing great, Mococo!
Go, Mococo! Watch out!
Yay! Go, Mococo!
How did you do, Mococo?
Ah, you did really great!
Zombies should never catch me!
I think with you, we have enough.
You got 12 points!
12 points!
That's 18 plus... that's 30, right?
Mococo, high five! High five!
I can get negative points.
You can get negative points.
So it's still up to Nerissa.
Don't hit anything, Nerissa!
She's not going to ruin it all, right?
Well, you know what, guys?
I have a driver's license.
So I'm not worried about this at all.
But there's a bunch of zombies, Nerissa!
I'm not scared of zombies.
That's what you say now.
Go, Nerissa!
Okay, wait, slow start.
Nice, nice, nice!
Whoa!
That's excellent!
Wait, wait, wait, wait!
Watch out, watch out!
I'm licensed! I can do this!
Second lap, second lap!
Drifting!
Look at her!
She's drifting!
Yeah!
Oh, watch out!
Really, really cool!
Careful, Nerissa!
I don't know if that went well.
But I feel like I probably did better than you guys, still.
Did you get negative points?
I only spun out three times!
Spun out three times is not allowed!
Oh, what are my points?
What's the silence for? Be real!
You got 9 points!
9 points!
Yay!
That means we passed, right?
Yes, we passed!
Pokey, we did it!
Hey, Pokey!
What do you say, huh? Do we get our deal?
Not bad!
As promised, interdimensional travel! All aboard!
Get in and go!
Wow, what a ride!
Let's crash it!
No, I have a better idea.
What idea?
Let's make a music video!
A music video?
Time to open up your eyes
Feel the music start to rise
Got to break the world and let me in
I know I was meant to be
Livin' life so fast and free
Try to keep your eyes on me
'Cause this is where my story all begins!
Livin' it up like crazy
Ready to play? Come at me
Carried away so easy
I can't get enough!
Free as a bird, no limit
Haven't you heard? I'm fearless
Get up and go, let's do this!
Watch me (watch me, watch me, watch me)
Watch me be your diva
I'm gonna raise your fever
Shakin' up all the crowd
Making some noise when I'm not allowed
Livin' my life out loud
I have awakened to wisdom beyond understanding
I keep indulging in my every whim
Oh, o-oh, o-oh
Don't blame me if I shine too bright
Can't help it if I start a fight
Oh, o-oh, o-oh
Now pay attention, please
'Cause this is only the beginning
It's our genesis!
Coming to wreak some havoc
How do you like this plot twist?
I'm embracing my madness
Can you hear it?
Whispers banging down your window
Oh yeah, oh yeah
Rumors reaching a crescendo
No humble beginnings, I'm destined for great things!
I'm sure you've heard of me by now
Whoah~
Midnight, draw me to the dark side
Oh yeah, oh yeah
Daylight, take me on a joyride
My crime is my passion
I'm mayhem in action
I know what day it is
This is our genesis
Gonna start the rave, when I misbehave, take center stage
Let the fun commence, but you know I'm gonna get intense
There are loopholes unspoken, the rules can all be broken
I'm runnin' on a rampage
The world is a blank page
I'm writing my story
In flames and in glory
They're gonna know me by name!
Oh, o-oh, o-oh
Is this my promised land?
The future's in my hands
Oh, o-oh, o-oh
But they don't understand
That I'm a star in the making, awaking and taking a bow
Tell me how you like me now
Come and watch me, watch me, watch me, watch me
Let your worries go
Gonna show you how to lose control, ready?
You've got to free your mind
Leave your restraint behind
Be outrageous
The chaos is contagious
Come on, you know what time it is!
It's our genesis!
Time to open up your eyes
Feel the music start to rise
Got to break the world and let me in
I know I was meant to be
Livin' life so fast and free
Try to keep your eyes on me
'Cause this is our beginning
It's our genesis!
Whispers banging down your window
Rumors reaching a crescendo
No humble beginnings, I'm destined for great things!
I'm sure you've heard of me by now
Whoah~
Midnight, draw me to the dark side
Daylight, take me on a joyride
My crime is my passion
I'm mayhem in action
I know what day it is
This is our genesis
You know what time it is?
It's our genesis!
Tell me what time it is!
Yeah! You know what time it is?
It's our genesis!
Tell me what time it is!
Everyone, look! It's the beach!
Look at this water! It's amazing!
Oh, this is nice! Yeah, I like it. It feels nice and breathable!
I want to see everyone close up though. This is our first time wearing something like this, so...
Bijou, why don't you show off what you've got to us?
Me first? Okay!
What are you looking at, huh? What are you looking at?
Fine, you can look a little bit, okay?
Here we go! Here's my skirt. You like the skirt?
Wow! It's so shiny!
They're like highlighters!
Kira-kira! I'm gonna blind you!
Sparkle-sparkle! I'm gonna blind you!
Oh! Don't look too close, you're gonna get blind!
Who wants to go next? Go, go!
This is kind of my first swimsuit, but I...
...what do you think?
The tail's so fluffy!
Opa!
Yeah! Ah, Shiori, come here!
Shiori Novella, ah! Shiori Novella...
...at your service! And look at my little ribbon!
Mocojyan! Okay, you can do this, Mocojyan.
Opa! Opa!
Yeah! Mocojyan, you can do it, Mocojyan!
Does it suit me? I tried to give you all some cute...
Look at those cute shorts!
She's so cute!
Mocojyan is so cute!
Now last, but...
...there's something a bit special on this outfit...
...don't you think? If you go down...
Oh! There it is! There it is!
Don't look there too much, but if you come up...
...you can see my waist and my top.
Armpits! / Yes, the pits!
But I see something strange off in the distance.
Just, just wait, let me go see.
Oh! It's a selfie stick!
Everyone, get behind me!
Let's take a picture together!
Nice! Yay!
Smile! Yay!
Oh, that helps!
Whoa! Cheese!
Uh, there's something down there in the sand.
What's that? I think that's an event trigger.
Oh, I stepped on it! Woof! Oh, step on it!
Careful!
Okay... um... / Let's go to the water!
Yay! Mocojyan, don't drown!
Run in slow-mo.
Let's just keep running on the beach!
Yeah! In slow motion!
In slow motion!
Let me go put this thing down, okay?
Selfie arm tired? / Yeah, selfie arm's losing it.
Thank you for being such a tall person. / Yeah, of course.
Oh my gosh, it's Pokey! Pokey!
Hey now! Save the beach party for later!
Sandcastles later, survival now! They already detected your dimension jump.
I thought we were supposed to be safe here.
We're in swimsuits, let us enjoy our time!
This is Justice we're dealing with! Expect the unexpected!
What should we do next then? Do we have to run forever?
Don't panic, I have a plan. Prove your bonds in the next trial, and I may assist you.
The power of friendship? Nakama power?
Well, if this is the beach episode, we have to do it, right?
Good. Something's been arranged. Look down! A & B!
A and B? What are you saying?
That's so lame! A or B?
C-Can it! Silence!
To confirm your bonds, you'll take on "Master of Advent."
Master of Advent! / What is that?
The rules are simple! Each participant will be asked a two-option question related to Advent.
You guys are Team Tomodachi, so it should be pretty easy, right...?
Yeah! Don't underestimate Advent!
Exactly. But incorrect answers mean... your bonds are weak, so I prepared a penalty game!
Penalty game?! / I didn't consent to this.
Yeah, a penalty game. Now, goth girl, take over.
Anyway! I think...
...that we're going to get one question, two answers, but only one is right.
And if you get it wrong, unfortunately, I think you're going to get muddied.
Muddied?!
But we've got new swimsuits!
Yeah, I don't want to get muddy in this thing!
So when you make your answer, I want you to hop there, okay?
Okay, I'll go first as an example.
Number one! Would I rather be...
...a vampire for A...
...or a werewolf for B?
On the count of three, okay?
One... Go!
Werewolf! Werewolf!
I don't wanna drink blood! What am I, stupid?
Aw, that's unexpected.
I seriously thought you were gonna say vampire.
You got that dog in you?
I got the dog in me, yeah!
Okay, okay!
Well, who is the winner?
I'll spray you in the face!
Go wash yourself!
You two, I'm watching you.
Well, you got us all wet, Shiori. Are you happy?
Not yet! Haha!
Next one! How about Mococo?
Moco-chan?
My turn!
Okay, wow! Here I go!
Um, at the beach, would I rather collect seashells, A...
...or, um... how was it? Make sandcastles, B?
Okay, figure it out! Ready?
Ready! Jump on three!
Three, two, one! Which is what?
I can't remember!
This was seashells and this was sandcastles.
Shiori is getting dirty!
Yeah, Shiori! No, I thought you wanted this one!
I made a mistake! I'd rather collect seashells...
...but I jumped this way! So that means, this way, this way!
That's not fair! Mococo!
Safe for now. Yeah, for now, for now!
Okay, have fun!
That is so mean!
Seriously!
It was a game of chance. Who's next?
Okay! Fuwawa's turn!
I don't get to get dirty this time, right? Yeah!
Okay, my question!
Do I prefer long-haired cats, or short-haired cats?
Okay, I'm the fluffy one, Fuwawa!
Here we go! Three, two, one!
What do you mean you prefer short hair?
It's so easy! It's a trick question!
It's so obvious! You're so mean to me!
Stinky point!
Ah, that feels nice. Yeah!
Well, it's gonna be your turn next. Oh my god!
Come back! I don't wanna play this game anymore!
Okay! Is it Bijou's turn now?
It's Bijou's turn! Bijou's turn!
Okay, my question is... Would I rather fight...
...one hundred chicken-sized hippos on A...
...or one hippo-sized chicken on B? Do you understand?
No! I understand! Okay, okay!
One hundred chicken-sized hippos...
...or one hippo-sized chicken?
Oh, this is actually a good one. Okay.
Okay, ready! And three, two, one!
Oh, Moco-chan!
Bijou doesn't like adds, Bijou likes boss battles! You should've known!
So hard, I'm almost...
Ah! I'm poisoning you!
Here comes a little bit of nasty!
Wait, C/C! C/C!
You have one chance to ask for mercy!
Don't bully me! Get sullied!
Ah! I'll sully you!
No! Don't look at me like this! Don't look at me, I'm hideous! No!
I'm going to the water! Goodbye, I'm going to the water!
Shiori's turn now. She became a mermaid.
She's swimming away. We'll never see her again.
Come back, Mococo-chan, we need you!
I am a mud demon now!
I'm back!
Last is my turn. Means I can't get it wrong, which feels pretty good.
Ahem, what's a good question? I'm not really sure. Let's see...
Nerissa is a demon, but she's also half raven.
If I had to pick between worlds and either be just a demon or just a raven...
So demon is B, raven is A. Which would I pick?
All right. Yes. Okay. On three, okay?
One, two, three!
I knew you would never give up being A! I can't be A!
I just think it would be great if I could have powers that aren't dependent on something that can break.
I thought being a demon is cooler though!
You know what's even cooler than being a demon?
You know what's even cooler than being a demon? Sullied Mococo!
I dare you! Being covered in mud!
Yeah, there you go!
Yeah, you wanna crawl with Nerissa?
I like mud, it's okay.
Why do you like it so much? Go take one in the ocean! Go in the ocean!
Not like this!
Well, we'll never see them again. Uh-oh. They're getting lost in the water.
Don't eat the salt water! Yeah, don't drink the water!
On the beach!
I'm gonna get rid of this.
That was so fun! Did we win?
[Pokey]: Hey hey hey hey hey!
[Pokey]: That didn't go so well, huh? Look how dirty you are!
[Pokey]: But hey, idols don't give up that easy, right?
[Pokey]: You are idols, right? Let's turn this around and shine again!
[Pokey]: And if you do... I'll take you somewhere super special—where even Justice can't find us!
No way! I want Justice to find me at some point!
Well, just for now! Just for now!
底々 底々 見つからないぜ
Bottom, bottom, can't be found!
パパイヤ マンゴー ココナツ
Papaya, mango, coconuts!
ココ☆ナツ!
Coco☆Natsu!
カキ氷 イチゴ味
Shaved ice, strawberry flavor!
ベロを出したら
Stick out your tongue...
まっかっか!
It's bright red!
Ai! 猛暑 酷暑 水着 SHOW! SAY!
Ai! Intense heat, severe heat, swimsuit SHOW! SAY!
ジャジャジャ ジャジャジャジャーン
Ta-da ta-da ta-da-da-da-da!
ココナツ!
Coconuts!
カチカチに燃えてるおひさま
The sun burning red-hot!
パッショバ ココナツ べいべー
Passioba coconuts baby!
待ちわびた季節は サマーサマー
The season we've waited for is summer, summer!
パッショバ ココナツ べいべー
Passioba coconuts baby!
思い切って 買っちゃった ビキニ
Taking the plunge and buying that bikini!
すっごーく 照れるけど
It's super embarrassing, but...
負けらんない!!
I won't give up!!
日焼け止め ココナツ セイバー
Sunscreen, coconut saver!
パッショバ ココナツ べいべー
Passioba coconuts baby!
紫外線 トコナツ レーザー
UV rays, everlasting summer laser!
パッショバ ココナツ べいべー
Passioba coconuts baby!
どっきゅーん ずっきゅーん
Ba-dump, ba-dump!
キミの視線
Your gaze...
心臓 大爆発☆
Heart, massive explosion☆
サシスセ ソコナツ べいべー
Sa-shi-su-se So-co-natsu baby!
ダディデュデ どこなつ べいべー
Da-di-dyu-de Do-ko-natsu baby!
かきくけ ココナツ べいべー
Ka-ki-ku-ke Co-co-natsu baby!
サン! サン! サマー タイム!
Sun! Sun! Summer time!
ココナツ
Coconut!
カキ氷 メロン味
Shaved ice, melon flavor
ベロを出したら ゾンビだ！ アイ！
Stick out your tongue, you're a zombie! Hi!
勝負浴衣着て BON DANCE! SAY!
Put on your best yukata and BON DANCE! SAY!
ジャジャジャジャジャジャジャジャーン
Ja-ja-ja-ja-ja-ja-ja-ja-nn!
ちょいなー ちょいなー ちょいなー ちょいなー
Choina, choina, choina, choina!
むしむしうんざり熱帯夜
Humid, unbearable tropical night
ココナツジュースみたいな
Just like coconut juice
長いようで 短い サマータイム
Summer time feels long, yet so short
やっちゃったもんがちっ！
First come, first served!
サシスセ ソコナツ べいべー
Sa-shi-su-se Coconut Baby
ダディデュデ ドコナツ？ べいべー
Da-di-du-de Where-nut? Baby
カキクケ ココナツ べいべー
Ka-ki-ku-ke Coconut Baby
サン！サン！サマータイム！ YES!
Sun! Sun! Summer Time! YES!
ファイヤー！
Fire!
ススス スパーキング！
S-s-s Sparking!
リリリリ レインボー！
R-r-r-r Rainbow!
フィーバー！
Fever!
ソイヤ ソイヤ ソイヤ ソイヤ！
Soiya, soiya, soiya, soiya!
アチアチのサマー
Piping hot summer
九十九里浜
Kujukuri Beach
アイス 激アマ
Ice cream super sweet
キャンプはさいたま
Camping in Saitama
サシスセ ソコナツ べいべー
Sa-shi-su-se Coconut Baby
ダディデュデ ドコナツ？ べいべー
Da-di-du-de Where-nut? Baby
カキクケ ココナツ べいべー
Ka-ki-ku-ke Coconut Baby
サン！サン！サマータイム！ YES!
Sun! Sun! Summer Time! YES!
どこ？そこ？あそこ？見つからないぜぇ？
Where? There? Over there? Can't find it!
パパイヤ マンゴー ココ☆ナツ！
Papaya, mango, Coco-nuts!
Huh? Huh?
Are we in our hideout?
Yay! We made it!
Nobody's in here!
Yeah, they can't find us here!
Well, unless I invite them over.
Don't invite them over! Okay, okay!
Isn't this our first time showing it in 3D to the audience?
Yeah!
Do you want to see our favorite parts?
Yeah! Show us, show us!
Look at all the candles!
We have a romantic ambiance, you know?
Yeah, very romantic!
But that's not all!
I have a favorite part too, you know.
If you look up there...
Whoa!
What light through yonder window breaks...
Wow, the moon is beautiful tonight.
月が綺麗ですね
"The moon is beautiful, isn't it?"
Well, about my favorite part...
Look behind you!
Huh? What?
This collection... It's all of my...
[Bleep]
...trinkets that we've collected over the years!
And her [Bleep]! Yes!
But also...
Look at our couch!
It's where FuwaMoco sits here!
Aren't they so cute?
What? What's wrong?
Weren't FuwaMoco wearing those?
Yeah, but they're right...
FuwaMoco? Guys?
We're here!
I hear your voices, but I do not see a body!
I think they're hiding!
No, wait, wait...
Dogs!
Bau bau!
Aw, they're so cute! Wait a second.
Yeah! Wait, where are the voices coming from, from the dogs?
I think this might be FuwaMoco?
What?! Wait, does that mean...
FuwaMoco have been turned into Dobermans?!
Oh my god!
Yeah, you know, I think they actually look more like hellhounds like this, don't you think?
Give 'em a big pet!
Yoshi yoshi! Good dog! You're a good girl!
Good dog! Good dog! You're a good girl!
Yeah, good girl! Good girl!
But wait, why are they Dobermans all of a sudden? What happened?
[Pokey]: Hahaha!
[Pokey]: Hehehe! Not so fluffy and fuzzy now, hoeh!
Pokey, change us back down! We can't eat donuts like this!
[Pokey]: That's why you wanna turn back? Hmph, whatever.
[Pokey]: I'll give you one final trial! Clear it, and I'll restore them!
Moco-chan, that means we can go back to normal!
Okay, everybody help us, please! I guess we'll give you one donut for the rescue!
Eh? Just one donut? One each or...?
Sharing! Eh, but I kind of like you like this though.
Well, Pokey, what kind of challenge are you going to give us today?
[Pokey]: FUWAMOCO Fukuwarai!
フワモコ福笑い！
FUWAMOCO Fukuwarai!
[Pokey]: Behold, the challenge before you!
The carpet has changed! Why do they have no faces? That's kind of scary.
Yeah, it is. I like it. Creepy!
[Pokey]: Hehe, ever heard of Fukuwarai?
[Pokey]: It's this old-school Japanese game — lemme show you how it's played.
[Pokey]: See those two giant faces? Their face parts are all scattered around.
Oh, I see, I see.
[Pokey]: Bijou and Shiori will be blindfolded and carry the face parts!
Blindfolded? Ooh, nice! Oh yeah, that sounds like fun!
Huh? We don't have to do anything.
[Pokey]: Big bird, with your words alone, you must guide them.
[Pokey]: Lead them to place each piece... and restore FUWAMOCO's face!
Me? Yeah, you.
Yeah, we're just gonna chill. Good luck! Okay, I'll do my best.
No pressure! No pressure!
[Pokey]: You've got 5 minutes. Better make it count!
Okay, let me say FUWAMOCO together!
Okay, let's all say FUWAMOCO together!
Or not! Let's go!
All right, ladies. So first plan of action: come on over, one on each side of me, pretty please.
And then I would like you to turn around. Oh, okay.
So, I have prepared for you blindfolds, so I'm gonna go ahead and just... you can feel free to adjust them as you'd like.
But that way you won't be able to see anything since I have to direct you, so go ahead and turn back around!
I cannot see a thing!
Yes, perfect. That's exactly what we want. Aha!
All right. And then we're gonna go ahead and start placing these things. So FUWAMOCO, my puppies, I'll do my best for you, okay?
Do your best! Do your best!
Okay, and... start!
Okay, so what I'm gonna do is I'm gonna hand you guys each a piece, and then I'm gonna tell you where to go.
Who goes first then? So you're each gonna do one face. Okay.
So you're gonna start that way...
Wait, where is it? Where am I? Shiori's just grabbing. I don't know what I'm gonna grab!
Okay, so Shiori, walk to me. Just walk to the sound of my voice.
Walk where? Yeah, yes! This way, this way! Walk towards me.
Okay, okay. If I accidentally grab something, I'm sorry.
Okay, grab onto... this. This. This. Yes.
Okay, don't move. Okay? Don't move?
Biboo, I want you to walk to the sound of my voice, okay?
Where is the sound of your voice? Just follow the sound of the voice!
Right... your right, your right. Okay, just a little right. Okay, forward!
Quickly! Okay, now come to me. Where is 'you'?
Okay, so I want you to grab this. Oh yeah, I got it. Yes.
So pretty much where you are right now... uh, not you Shiori. Okay, Shiori come forward a little bit.
This forward or this forward? The forward towards me.
This forward? Okay, that's too much. Back up just a little bit.
And then I want you to move...
You're running out of time! Your... your right! Your right! Right!
This is right! Left! Left! Okay, back up!
Moco-chan, I don't know if this is gonna work out! Place it down!
I felt strong, but now I'm regretting that!
Place it down, Biboo. Oh, down? Okay.
Okay, forward a little bit.
Wait!
Okay, and then can you straighten it out?
Like this?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, just a little bit more.
Wait! Wait! Wait!
Okay, yeah, and then can you just...
...scoot the whole thing over to...
...the right?
No, left!
What about me? Should I do the same thing?
No! No! Other way!
Okay, three big steps!
What are you doing?
Okay, next item! Next item!
Is that where we put it?
Stay right where you are.
Stay right where you are. I am here where I am.
I've got two, okay?
I got two, yes.
I don't think this is heading...
How did I do?
Lapis! Do you have eyes?
I want you both... Yes.
I want you both to walk backwards, okay?
How many steps?
Maybe straighten out a little bit.
Okay, that's definitely good.
Okay, back?
No, actually you're perfect, Shiori.
Bibu, you better get running.
I know I'm perfect.
Place one down.
Which one?
This one! Or this one!
Keep going, keep going! You're going too far!
Start over again!
What? Where are we going?
This one's okay, right?
No, move it over to the right.
Move it to the right!
Okay, place the other one down!
I don't want to... I don't want it to continue like this!
Okay, move it...
Trust me!
This way! No.
Where I am.
This way! Yeah.
All the pieces have to be like this!
Okay Bibu, come towards the sound of my voice.
Where is the sound of your voice?!
I think it's over here!
Forward, forward.
Okay, stop. Now come this way a little bit. Turn...
Walk this way!
You hear where I am?
Oh, yes, yes.
Pretend you're in an immersive game.
I hear it, I still hear it!
Stop, stop, stop.
Now I want you to turn a little bit this way.
Wait, why? This is aligned!
Rotate your body! Rotate me!
And this is all wrong!
Now I want you to place the one in your left hand down, okay?
On the ground.
Like this?
Yeah, okay. Now I want you to walk slightly in this direction.
Just like crab walk.
Where is this going?!
See where I'm at?
Like an immersive game. It's like a game, Bibu.
Place it down.
Place it down!
I'm doing my best!
So what? No.
You have one minute.
One more, okay.
Okay, I'm going.
Okay, now where?
So, Bibu...
Walk this way.
Okay, put it down.
Right there.
Wait, no, that's the wrong way! Pick it back up!
Walk... opposite side!
Put it down!
Okay, uh...
...behind you! Move backwards, backwards, backwards, backwards!
Backwards, backwards!
Okay, down! Perfect!
At least my face looks a bit better than Fuwawa's.
Okay, now walk this way.
This way? Yeah, yeah. Now, now walk...
...to your left.
30 seconds!
No, no, sorry! Right! I figured you'd mess up, so...
This way! This way, this way!
This way! Yes, okay, now forward.
I think this is going so well!
Now put it down.
So good.
It's so clean!
15 seconds left!
Are you done?
Make it work! Make it work by force!
Yeah, yeah, yeah! 15 seconds. Don't worry about it. Don't worry about it.
Are we done?
Yeah!
Yay!
Okay, I want you guys to turn on around...
...and we're going to take off your blindfolds so you can see how you did, okay?
Wait, which way's around?
This way!
Huh?
Well, let's take a look.
I bet we did great.
Yeah.
Yeah?
It's...
Pokey, what do you think? Isn't it good?
Hey, Bijou, Shiori! You sure this is Fuwawa and Mococo?
Yeah, look at it!
Some of it seems a little...
Nah, nah, that's...
I think it's great!
Is it upside down or anything?
I think it looks perfect! Why are you like this?
I'm not saying anything bad!
You know we can get better!
That's not my face!
It's perfect! It's just...
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
What if I put this over here?
I'm going to put it there.
That's my face like...
Yeah!
Babu!
Yeah! It's great!
I made a decision, you see, to do it like this because...
...I just wanted to see what it would look like a little lower.
This is not good!
Well, is it good enough to get changed back, Pokey?
Yeah.
Hmph, fine. I'll change them back!
Yay! We're back!
We're not animals anymore!
Huh? Huh?
Yay!
Oh, they're normal!
You didn't make my dream come true...
That's not good, no no no...
It's okay, I like you better this way.
Look at my face!
I'm really glad we could get through this together. Aren't you guys?
Yeah! Power of friendship!
As Advent, you've gotta keep working together and looking out for one another!
Yeah, that's karma, yeah, get down
Checkmate, I'm a superstar. Stay insane, but you rock with it, ah
Yeah, like 24/7, I'm a hot mess ya, love-hate. Get less boring, oh my god
ホームラン バタバタ swing my shot, ah, like a villainous villainess, bring home the jackpot
Home run, flappin' around, swing my shot, ah, like a villainous villainess, bring home the jackpot
勇者も悪役も変わらない
Heroes and villains are no different
派手にブチかまそう
Let me hit it hard and flashily
Life's just a tightrope, why not stop to fool around?
"Chaotic good" is peak right now, I can show ya how
Don't get confused, we are not the same
I'm a ruthless dame
"Good vs Evil" is so overdone
Let's all kick back and party, just leave it to moi
Loosen my lips, loosen my li-li-lips, yeah, that's karma, ta-da
Loosen my lips, I'm about to say some ish, get it, yeah, that's karma, ta-da
Sorry I'm just better, sorry we're go-getters
Ain't my fault we're wicked, stunning, tricky, why you running?
Bet'cha think you're clever, whatever
Talk about a "kumbaya", hey-yo, checkin' this out
フルボッコんぼっちゃって 欲望召し上がれ
Beat 'em to a pulp and dig into your desires
アイ$ハート get down ウィンク See yonara サイコですわ
Eye-heart, get down, wink, sayonara, it's total psycho
ドメスティック ドラマチック 愛しき人々 この指とまれ
Domestic, dramatic, beloved people, gather around my finger
ハードにハートはハイになって
Hard heart gets high
弾けて恥じらい捨てちゃえ
Burst out and throw away your shyness
叫び踊り 誇れ激動的show体 酔いしれてちょうだい
Scream and dance, be proud of this turbulent show form, get drunk on it
道化のパラダイス 惹かれ合う感覚が共鳴共鳴
Jester's paradise, mutual attraction resonating
"Good vs Evil," but I'm which one? Just stuck here in the middle, that's not any fun
Loosen my lips, loosen my li-li-lips, yeah, that's karma, ta-da
Loosen my lips, I'm about to say some ish, get it, yeah, that's karma, ta-da
想像から創造 衝動から猛攻
From imagination to creation, from impulse to fierce attack
ほらあっという間に華麗に変身 変幻自在
Look, in a flash, a splendid transformation, endlessly versatile
毒々しい本能 喰らえ咆哮 Run, talk about a "kumbaya, baya"
Venomous instinct, take this roar! Run, talk about a "kumbaya, baya"
Talk about a "kumbaya", sorry I'm just better
Sorry we're go-getters, ain't my fault we're wicked, stunning, tricky, why you running?
Bet'cha think you're clever, whatever
Talk about a "kumbaya"
異世界 queen, switch チューニング マイナー カラフル に cacophony
Isekai queen, switch tuning minor, colorful cacophony
歪 で 優雅 に ハチャメチャ Welcome to Miss Fortune's game
Distorted, elegant, and chaotic, welcome to Miss Fortune's game
Well, that was Go-Getters! How did you like the performance?
To everybody watching right now, we have some big news!
And guess what? For our second anniversary, we have two big announcements!
The first one is... a brand new song!
The second original song in the story of Advent, PRISONER, will be released on August 31st at 12 AM local time in each region!
- It's just Prisoner!
- What's the matter?
It's gonna sound great!
Yeah! And if you want to find out,
don't go anywhere because you'll be redirected
to the music video right after this stream!
- Yeah!
- That's right!
And guess what?
We're also set to premiere
the new song right after this!
Yeah!
All right, everybody! Are you ready?
- Places! Places!
- Okay!
Okay...
Locked away where nightmares keep you awake,
You'll be safe within my crushing embrace
(You're all mine, all mine)
You'll never escape...
Wayward soul, I'll wrap you up in darkness
that consumes you whole,
Hold you in my labyrinth of walls
(Lost in the depths that swallow you,
where just your shadows follow you)
Always churning in the deep, I won't let you sleep
You don't need your dreams now that you belong to me
Throw them all away, you're too frail to be free
(You will always be)
My lovely prisoner (Are you shaking?)
My eyes will find you, let me clutch you tightly
(You can only be mine)
Poor little prisoner (Are you breaking?)
My chains will bind you here forever,
Stay here for all time
In tenebris
In frigore
In carcere
Close your eyes, go deeper
in the emptiness that plagues your mind,
Let my dark envelop your light
I will keep you safe and sound,
hear the blissful silence all around
I'll drag you down below, never let you go
Everything you've been, the transgressions of your past;
Throw them all away, let me hold you at last
My lovely prisoner
(What's the matter?)
You're never leaving, you are mine forever
(Got to keep you right here)
Poor, helpless prisoner
(Did you shatter?)
Why are you grieving your ambitions?
Let them disappear
I can hear your plea, reaching desperately,
But I'll never, ever set you free
Stay with me...
My lovely prisoner
(Are you shaking?)
My eyes will find you, let me clutch you tightly
(You can only be mine)
Poor little prisoner
(Are you breaking?)
My chains will bind you here forever,
Stay here for all time
In tenebris
In frigore
In carcere
Yeah! That was our new song, "Prisoner"!
- What did you think of the track, huh?
- Hot song, huh?
Yeah!
Okay, and let's all move on to the second piece
of exciting news! Getting close, girls!
hololive English -Advent-
2nd Anniversary Celebration!
First up, we have...
...the Frame Art Board!
It's a large illustration board framed beautifully.
The luxurious frame features our logo
with foil stamping for extra shine.
It's a perfect item to decorate your home and to
enjoy looking at every single day, so you can see
all of us together, just like we should be!
Well, next up, we have a
Sticker Set (Halloween 2024 ver.)!
Yeah!
Five different designs! And it includes the VRChat
design released for Halloween, plus a 3-piece
sticker set featuring each Advent member's
original design! And then you can put them on
your phone, stick them on your PC,
and have fun with them!
- Yeah!
- All right, next up, we got...
...the Connecting Charms! Yeah! What's awesome
is that all these charms can actually connect...
...to each other,
so you can mix and match for...
all kinds of different ways, right?
And have fun!
Yeah!
Finally,
we've got the Varsity Jacket!
Wow!
It's got the Advent logo on the back,
and Polky is embroidered on the front chest area too!
And...
guess what?
What?
You can actually attach those charms
I just showed you
on the zipper of the jacket too!
Awesome!
You know, it's a cool item that you can rock
both in your everyday life
and at events too!
Yeah!
And guess what?
What?
It's happening right now!
The merch just dropped at the hololive Official Shop!
Now! Now!
And hey guys, notice that guide showing up
on the bottom...
the bottom left, left of the YouTube screen?
Go ahead and click it to shop your favorites, okay?
Click, click, click, click!
This was such a wonderful day together. We had so much fun!
Yeah!
Even though we were running from Justice half the time...
Well, yeah, typical Friday!
Were we really worried?
No, better luck next time, Justice!
As if you could ever catch us!
We are so fast!
And can you believe that?
We've been together for two years now!
Yeah, can you believe it?
That's a lot of memories!
Yeah, lots of memories, and...
we're looking forward to all of the next years together!
Year 3!
Year 4!
Year 5!
Year 6!
Yeah!
Forever!
Together!
Off on an adventure!
Bye-bye!